This is JoJo's Bizarre Adventure.
In the 19th century, as the United States
of America explored its vast continent,
the greatest conquest was
that of the western frontier.
It beckoned
and a desire called
America sped across the map
claiming native lands as its own
till it reached the wide Pacific?
Get him!
The bastard's got it coming!
He had white men's books
hidden in his tent!
I've seen it myself!
How the hell is he so fast?
Look, he's running the
same way the white men do!
He...
he ran it!
It was there, in the west,
where the Santa Ana headwinds
blow in from Mexico,
that people gathered
in the summer of 1890,
every one of them, in search of something.
Hey, which one of you left all
that mess in the shitter, huh?
It's my tech, you love it!
Center trap!
I was here first!
Welcome to the first ever Steel Ball Run!
This epic trek, which will commence here
in San Diego and end in New York City,
will be the first ever
to have its participants
cross North America while on horseback!
4,000 mind-boggling miles.
At the end of the race's nine stages,
our victor will receive a
peerless prize of $50 million.
Many racers will vie for these riches,
but only one will walk away the winner.
A question, Mr. Steele.
Baron Rucatugo from Germany says he
intends to compete from atop an automobile?
Indeed.
and with my blessing for what is
America if not a land of progress.
If he wants to trust a machine, then
that is a good baron's prerogative.
The $150 entry fee has been called
a money-making scheme by some.
You wound me, sir.
We are covering the medical
expenses of any racer
who meets with misfortune
during the endeavor.
However, each racer is
responsible for their own safety.
We acknowledge their right to bear arms,
enshrined as it is within the Second
Amendment of the Constitution.
The race will go down as a failure if
no one makes it to the finish line.
If that should occur, what do you
think your investors will have to say?
Probably just kill me.
That was a joke.
Okay.
You speak to me of failure,
then I will speak in turn.
There is no failure worse than
turning your back on adventure.
To perish in bed untested, having
never faced the impossible?
and carried the day.
Come what may, this race
is a triumph of the spirit.
Our racers don't know
the meaning of failure.
No matter how the days ahead may unfold?
The steel ball run will be
a race the likes of which!
the world has never laid eyes upon.
What am I gonna do, Lucy?
I'm so scared right now.
What if the whole thing falls apart?
It's all my fault!
Steven, you'll be okay.
After all, you've been a promoter
for 40 years, haven't you?
Have faith, sweetheart.
I know it'll all work out.
Okay, I'll try to be brave.
Atta boy.
Okay, I'm guessing you're here to
sign up for the race, ain't ya?
Gonna need your John Hancock.
We'll take your fingerprints and
horse's nose prints on the first day.
Just know you can't swap out the
jockey or the horse down the road.
Taddlecloth and your entry certificate.
Hmm?
Gyrocephaly.
Oh, oh.
Neil?
Oh.
Those are some unusual
baubles you got there.
They do something or
are they just for show?
Ah!
Oh!
My legs.
What did you...
Damn it!
What did you do to me, huh?
I was just curious about
those balls or whatever.
I didn't mean no harm
that right hey clerk how
much of my entry fee is
on the counter huh if
the money's all there
why then I guess I've got
no quarrel with you oh
you came up short $20 but
I did pay the full amount
didn't I still hadn't
given you your receipt
nothing's official till
I do I wonder where that
cash might have run off
to you're going to give
back what you pilfered?
Because if you don't, they won't
let me compete in the race.
And that would mean I don't win.
Understand?
Oh, he's a thief!
Security, come quick!
Just give me my damn receipt.
What happened?
Caught him thieving.
Hey, Valkyrie.
Sorry for the wait.
Time to find a tent and make
myself at home for a while.
Look at me, dammit!
I ain't done with you yet!
No way, no how!
Whatever shit you pulled in there,
I'd like to see you try that again!
Quit your wriggling!
See that?
Now you die!
Man, fool's got a hold of my gun!
Little bastard!
Food for thought, Goldteeth!
If I wanted you dead, you'd
be warm food right now!
Well, you act all high and mighty, but
you never saw me grabbing those coins!
I got the law sicked on me
for nothing more than a guess!
And that I cannot abide!
Good news, pal!
I'm joining the race!
That way you'll never see me coming!
Only thing you're joining is a
chain gang. Enough. Let him go.
Huh?
I'm not pressing charges.
Don't lock him up.
There's no need for that.
Let him go.
And give him a gun.
Pick it up take it take it
and see what happens next.
We're out of our league
here where's the sheriff?
I think we're about to see some bloodshed.
What's all the fuss about? Hey!
Get out of the way already!
I can't see a damn thing!
Come on!
You didn't think I
meant all that, did you?
I was kidding! No harm done!
I, uh, I don't much like the
way you're looking at me.
See?
I wasn't gonna hurt you none honest.
Yeah, best of luck in the race.
Nobody move.
Just one of you boys up to.
You're lucky I didn't do worse.
I would find a doctor for
that arm if I were you.
And drop the gun while you're at it.
Somebody could get hurt
Sheriff what do we do now?
Just another duel nothing
to lose sleep over a
Duel both men agreed to so it goes.
Duel my ass.
I'm not even sure what happened.
That ball he threw.
It was spinning fast.
So fast that it dug right into his arm.
And even that didn't slow it down.
Hey, wait up.
What's that steel ball about?
I need to see it again.
Hand it over. No, don't.
It's still spinning, damn it!
What was that?
My legs.
Just then I was...
I was standing.
No! Wait!
Let me through!
Get out of my way!
Move it, you old bastard!
What'd you come from?
Shut up!
Please!
What did you do to me?
I need to know what that was just now!
You're gonna tell me everything!
Top cause of death. Wanna take a guess?
Mosquito-borne diseases
are killer number one.
But getting kicked by a horse
is definitely the runner-up.
You trying to get him to switch
places on the podium or what?
Don't get your hopes up. I mean it.
You standing up from that chair
was nothing more than coincidence.
A muscle spasm, that's all.
A spasm?
It was the steel ball. I know it!
Please let me touch it again!
I can pay you!
I'm done with this little conversation.
Hey, you mouthy brat.
Did you think I was
going to let that slide?
Well, all right then.
If you won't hand over the ball
to me, I'll take it my dance now!
My fingers!
I guess there's no harm in
giving you a bit of credit.
You're sporting some pretty
well-conditioned muscles up above,
quite a feat considering.
But it doesn't change anything.
The spin of the steel balls won't
magically let you walk again.
They can't just give you your legs back.
I'm supposed to believe that
after what I've seen them do?
No matter what it takes, I'm going to
figure out the mystery of the spin!
When you can't even ride a horse,
I'll be gone in two days' time.
Got a cross-country
race that needs winning.
Hey, come on! Damn it all!
Who's in the way now, huh?
Maybe you'll watch your mouth
next time, you little shit.
Scram already. Roll on home.
I wonder why I came to
this beach in San Diego.
Was it just to witness the
start of the steel ball run?
Or was it?
My name is Johnny Joestar.
My father was a rancher and
a well-known horse trainer.
So all of my life, horses
have been by my side.
Watching their muscles
work from atop the saddle,
hearing their hooves strike the ground?
it was beautiful.
Whenever they ran, it felt like I could
understand their thoughts and emotions.
Like we shared a connection.
Beautiful things demand our attention.
And if it's something dynamic and alive,
too, there's nothing more captivating.
Young master Johnny has talent.
So said the old stable
hand, and I believed him.
But my father remained aloof.
For my older brother Nicholas
was already a rising star.
Until an accident
claimed his life one day.
and everything changed.
After his death, I began racing horses
in earnest and won time and time again.
They started calling me a prodigy.
With each new victory, more
people would gravitate to me,
paying homage with their flattery,
their gifts, their money.
To win a race on horseback was a triumph.
Mastering oneself and the beast
below, it felt like manifest destiny.
But destiny had something else in mind.
Just you wait.
Once you see how dazzling she is,
you won't make fun of me anymore.
Is Dorothy Parker that great?
I'm telling you, Johnny.
The day will come when the world
treats actresses like works of art.
I guess that would explain the
crowd I've been waiting in line.
You know?
Yeah, so I've been in
line since yesterday.
Oh yeah.
And look what it got.
The end of the line is back there!
I've been here all night!
You can't just cut in!
You need to shut up already!
No one gives a shit that
you pulled an all-nighter!
Hey, someone had better
tell me what's going on.
I was standing in line fair and square when
this guy walked up and tried to cut in.
What?
By the way, this is Johnny Joestar.
I knew you were the coolest, Johnny!
Seriously, is this
thing worth the trouble?
Aw, come on!
You again?
You don't know when to quit, do you?
What the hell did you do to me?
My whole life changed yet again.
Nurse!
I need you!
What are you, stupid? Come here.
Help me, damn it.
I'm shitting myself over here,
and there's nothing I can do.
Hey, hurry up and clean
this shit off of me.
It's your goddamn job, isn't it?
What the hell is this
tube going into my leg?
Come on, you dumb son of a...
Quiet, or I'll give you
something you can yell about.
What do you care if I tap
you for a couple of pints?
Not like you can feel your legs anyway.
What's the problem here?
Ain't it crazy that you've never
had one visitor the whole time?
Not even your own? Father!
It makes people sick to look
at you, did you know that?
That's right, Mr.
Hot Shit Jockey.
Now you're covered in hot shit.
No matter what I will learn the secret
he's keeping and I will
ride a horse again.
So what do you think Valkyrie seen
any horses we should be worried about?
Me I don't think we'll have any trouble.
Don't tell me he's still trying.
Been at it since last night.
I heard he's gonna compete in the race.
I mean, I know the guy used
to be a famous jockey and all,
but I feel so bad for him.
Him being the horse.
Oh, hit like that had to hurt for sure.
He trying to regain his
former glory or what?
Good way to get killed.
Oh, I'd be screaming if that were me.
They say he got injured bad, and he
can't feel pain down there that horse!
He bought isn't helping things any it's
old hot-blooded and got a hell of a temper!
Look it?
He's gotta stop this you
agree with me, don't you I?
Only saw what happened to him right
now, but in my professional opinion.
There's no way he's riding that thing
Not down a working pair of legs.
Let me put it this way if you can ride
that horse then he's stubborn as all hell.
I want to enter the
race is that right gotta
pay the entry fee with
legal american tender.
So can you pay or can't you
huh this is a a giant emerald.
Certificate in Saddlecloth.
We'll take your horse's nose
print right before the start, sir.
Don't have one.
What?
I will cross the continent and win
using only the legs I was born with.
To get that prize money, I'll
beat them at their own gain.
Tomorrow is the big day.
Uh...
Uh... No? No?
Ladies and gentlemen,
we're minutes away from the start of the
first ever race across
the length of America,
the Steel Ball Run.
The atmosphere down here at the beach
is a heady blend of anticipation,
ambition, and horse poop.
Now, here come the jockey's
most favorite to win the race.
The cowboy hailing from
Wyoming, Mountain Tim.
Atop his trusty steed, Shadow Rider.
The Mongolian master of
horsemanship himself, Dot Han.
His horse's name is number one.
The nomad from the Sahara, Urm Davdal.
He intends to race on a camel,
if you can believe that.
And now, appearing atop the
tried and true silver bullet,
proudly bearing Saddle Cross 001,
the heir apparent of British
horse racing, Diego Brando!
The first stage of the
race is the simple 10
-mile circuit ending in the
shadow of an old church.
The winner of today's leg will
receive a one-hour time bonus,
as well as a $10,000 prize.
And with that, I welcome you to the first
ever opening day of the Steel, The Run!
Take note, my lucky observers, we
shall move once the race is underway.
Thanks to the special locomotives, we
shall follow the race in the lap of luxury.
Hey, look, the idiot from before.
He's pat as a hair or dead.
Damn to hell.
I won't give up on this.
I have to figure it out.
I'm going to learn the
secret of those steel balls.
No matter what.
You chose the right horse
for the race. At least.
An old horse knows what it's about.
It won't rush to the head of the pack
and sprain a leg from all the excitement.
You're interesting, so here's a hint.
You already know the
answer to this question.
If you have enough will to ride a horse,
then why don't you put it into action?
Yo!
Two minutes until the starting gun!
Please, Fool, lick me
one more time. Come on!
One more time.
Spin!
It's time for the Steel Ball Run to begin!
10 a .m.
September 25th, 1890, on the first
transcontinental race across North America,
the Steel Ball Run is finally underway.
Huh?
Are you seeing this?
How's he controlling the horse
if he can't even use his legs?
If I'm with you, I can do this.
The spin, I'll uncover
in secret, or die trying.
And they're off, neck and
neck, all keeping to the pack.
No surprise, the first stage is only 10
miles, but that's nothing to sniff at.
If the jockeys don't pace themselves,
they can wear out their
horses here on day one.
Hold on.
Someone's shooting
ahead. Saddle clock. 636.
Faster and faster.
He's running like the wind down there.
Who is it?
636 is Gyro Zeppeli.
Is he insane?
Who runs their horse that hard
right off the starting line?
No way is he going to make it
to New York riding like this.
But he said he was going to win.
Said that's what he came here to do.
We're swerving. No good.
I can't afford to get
tangled up between these two.
Two riders are down.
This may be the end of
their steel ball run, folks.
The rules of the race do allow
for ramming one's opponents.
Look, another jockey has
broken away from the pack.
It's Diego Brando,
the heir apparent of the British
horse racing world is closing in fast!
Weights, and he's not alone!
Another racer is searching ahead!
Hell for leather!
Scrooge Abdel and his colossus of a camel!
My steed weighs 50 % more than yours!
There's not a horse alive
that can withstand this!
A cloche for gyro!
Diego Brando presses the advantage!
60 minutes of bonus time and
$10,000 will belong to me,
En-Dabdol!
What the?
And Abdahl is down how did
he miss that cactus patch
it's plain as day I don't
think he's getting up folks
Ermd Abdahl a favor to win is unexpectedly
knocked out in the first stage
It's Gyro's steel ball.
I don't understand how it works,
but he used one of his steel
balls to locate a bunch of cacti?
and then he lured the
camel rider right into it.
Fascinating.
Not only the balls, but
they're wielded, too.
I'll take what I can get in life,
so long as it's not contagious?
and that goes double for extra time.
What the hell?
Hey, uh, it isn't 10 yet, right?
What?
I cannot believe this!
I overslammed?
I can't refund your entry fee.
Nah, I'm good.
Gotta be in the race to
win that 50 million, right?
Uh-huh.
I'm gonna win the whole ball of quacks!
Of course I am!
I'm captain of my own destiny
and a smooth telling ahead, yo!
Uh, some weirdo just started the race.
Guess we should mark it down.
Saddle clock 777.
Name's Poco Loco. Whoa!
Is it my birthday or something?
Cause this ground is super smooth!
The other horses already pounded it down.
It sure wouldn't feel this even if
we started racing when we should've.
Poco Loco is on fire today!
Yo, yo, yo, yo!
Now that I think it through,
At 400 yards per liter of fuel,
we're not going to make it.
How regrettable.
Shall we return to our
homeland, my dear Baron?
Gyro Zeppeli still holds
the lead with Diego Brando,
also known as Dio, not far behind.
That jockey, his movements
have been odd for a while.
Chasing to the right,
closing in to the left,
slowly shrinking the gap
between him and Gyro.
And again. But how?
Could Dio have discovered it?
He's gone.
To hell with your tricks, Dio.
Show yourself.
He caught up the gyro in no time at all!
What devilry is this?
It didn't look like his horse sped up any.
I was a bit surprised by
your trick with the camel,
but now I deem you no
more than a rank amateur.
I see how this will unfold.
Gyro's horse has a tell,
and Dio, he figured it out!
You're so easy to read.
Everyone has their tells,
and horses are no exception.
Maybe one switches its
tail about before charging,
or runs wide when it feels cornered.
The shake of a head, the angle of a back.
Races are won and lost on
the secrets those can betray.
This horse's habit is specific indeed.
Five, six, seven, and here we go.
Yes, it sways slightly to the left
every eight breaths like clockwork.
That lateral motion
results in a loss of speed.
If I increase my speed
at that precise moment,
I can erase his lead without tiring out
my horse and then claim it for myself.
Dio's in front by half a length!
Dare to explain how you pulled that off?
It's called technique, you troglodyte.
Stay back there and
learn from your betters.
Level with me.
Are you insinuating my horse has a tell?
Would it even matter if I told
you habits are carved in stone?
Indelible like fate!
Dio is pulling ahead!
What's going on?
It doesn't look as though he's speeding
up, but he's definitely in front now.
Genius at work.
That's what you're observing.
It's no use.
Gyro won't be able to pass him again.
The gap's just going
to get wider and wider.
Eight miles to go in this leg of the race
as the pack clears a dried-up riverbed.
Hey, what's the big idea
of having a tell, huh?
That's news to me.
A lot of strong horses
and riders out here.
The same for the weak.
But you don't need to
change what you're about.
Now, I say you double down on it instead.
Looks like you're
swerving a bit down there.
Sure, hope that's not a habit.
Go ahead, though.
Do it all you want.
Keep swerving and see where it gets you.
The Brick, whose planks are giving way!
Gyrocephaly leaps, ice water in his veins!
Geo hesitates!
Bastard!
The other riders are
diverting across the riverbed,
but Geo is stuffed in his tracks!
It's just like before, with my legs!
The mysterious steel balls spin.
It amplified the horse's habit
with the burst of power! Yo, whoop!
Yo, yo, yo, yo!
You see that?
We got up to him!
Back to the pack right
now, but not for long.
Yo, yo, yo!
That cliff's looking pretty steep!
That ain't part of the god darn route.
Damn it all, we're here because of him!
He was charging ahead like a house
of fire and we got caught up in it.
Yeah, but take a look at the map.
If we can get across here,
it's a hell of a shortcut.
I ain't risking a good horse on that jump.
I'm going that-a-way. Screw this.
What to do?
Hell, you up too sprawled out like that.
Just counting the clouds.
Somebody's got to do it.
Fine.
What I meant to say was,
why the hell are you flopped on the ground
instead of helping me
do an honest day's work?
Three days ago now, this old
fortune-teller lady read my future.
Hmm,
she told me that the absolute
worst time in a person's life
is called the void of heaven
and earth But check this out.
Mine is the exact opposite right now.
I got the best luck
Without a doubt the next two months
will be the most fortunate period of
your entire life Only one in five
billion people have this kind of luck.
So put it to good use kid
You've got nothing to fear
the world's your oyster Ha-ha!
Well, let me tell you about
your first lucky break, then.
The owner of this field hired us to
get it ready for planting season.
Nah, I'm good.
I'm gonna live the easy life from now on.
Folks like us don't got
the luxury of living easy.
Aw, I just forgot what
number of clout I was up to.
Boss would've paid you
150 thanks to me putting
in a good word and here
you are acting a damn fool.
Huh.
Hey, you're Gramps, that field
work you were going on about.
How much did you say it pays?
Here I am, yo.
Now I'm galloping out of
San Diego with my faithful
Steve and my one in five
billion lucky streak.
I'm gonna win this thing.
And when I do, I'm
grabbing that prize money!
I'm going straight home and
doing a whole lot of nothing!
Throw a lasso if you have a rope.
Maybe you'll get lucky with it.
What the hell kind of legs
does that guy have on him?
But it's not like he just saved my life.
I'm back on solid ground thanks
to my top-shelf good luck.
That's all.
Hey! Yeah! Voodoo!
Only four miles to go in
this first stage of the race.
Gyro Zeppeli remains in the lead, but
will it be true with the finish line?
Hold on, Gyro's nearing way
off course toward the trees.
What manner of foley is this?
He's taking a shortcut.
If he charges through the woods, he could
gain at least 800 yards on the pack.
But sir, won't the trees
pose a hazard to him?
I'm glad they will.
He's gambling with his life.
How will the pack respond to this move?
If he gets away from me now,
I'll never catch up to him!
We've got a taker!
Now, two, three, six,
breaking for the trees!
Yee-haw!
Yo, yo, yo!
Hey, where's the leader of the pack?
I kind of got a late start.
Wait, you don't know?
Because we're about to follow
him straight into the tree line.
Pretty daunting, but good to kind
of look out back in these days.
Any shortcut is a good one.
Huh?
What the...
Is he nuts?
He's writing with his eyes closed.
Here I go!
An old Poco Loco.
Portis' favorite.
Missing every branch.
No sight, no fright.
What the hell's going on?
Horses dodge trees on their own,
but that jockey isn't even looking.
And nothing has touched him.
The odds of that are a million to one.
Where'd that guy come from?
And why are his eyes closed?
Something's fishy here.
I should take him off the board.
Two minutes since they went in there.
They should appear any second.
The first one out of the woods is Gyro.
Gyro Zeppeli is still in
the lead with no comers.
Wait, a second horse dragging
its rider by the stirrup.
Saddleclaw 777, register
to Poco Loco. What the?
From the ground,
Poco Loco was able to dodge the trees and
allow his mouth to take the quickest path.
You think I fell off, huh?
Oh, yeah!
I knew it!
This look of mine is taking
me all the way! Come on.
You've got to be kidding me.
Poco Loco emerges in second place.
The rest of the pack rounds the band
on the official room are behind.
This position isn't terrible.
The shortcut was worth it.
Incredible.
This race is always bang right
from the top just you wait the most
treacherous part of the route is
yet to come a Downhill stretch
2,000 yards long with steep
30-degree slopes and dizzying
hundred-foot drops How steep it's
not terrain fit for a locomotive,
so we'll take a slight detour accordingly
And now they face the
treacherous downhill stretch if
our jockeys go too fast here
the mounts can lose their
footing like that luckily they're
all holding steady keeping
this pace is a true testament
to a writer's skill nice
and slow we gotta take it
easy on this part nice and
slow don't tell me you're
chickening out now mr lucky huh
who's there i ain't chickening
out of nothing put it to
good use kid you got nothing to
fear the world's your Oyster!
Yeah, that's right.
The old woman said I had nothing to fear.
If the world's my oyster,
then I better get cracking!
Take a nap, old timer!
Poco Loco's breaking away!
He's all caught up and then some!
Choc-a-fly!
Yo, yo, yo!
Lucky and an idiot. Good to know.
Keep it together!
Don't get riled up!
They're searching ahead!
The horses saw the leader pick up
speed and can't help themselves.
A co-level is fresh on
the downsole, folks.
The devil is taking his
due today. It's okay.
You're doing your thing.
Nothing can snap us down.
Poco Loco is down.
Gyro takes the lead.
Hey, kid. Much obliged.
Poco Loco tempted fate and paid the piper.
Huh?
What in the blue hell?
Wait!
Poco Loco and his horse are going
strong and none the worse for wear!
It almost looks as though
they were to top something!
Who is this guy?
It's a dead cow! He's cooking!
Yeah!
I prefer my steak with a little more meat
on the bone, but I ain't complaining!
He takes the lead!
This race is getting more
bizarre by the minute.
Does he have some kind
of ability no I don't
give a damn what kind
of moves He's packing
last night checked this
is a horse race you
switch to a skeleton and
I've got a bone to pick
One rock slide coming right up he hits any
of those and his cows out to pasture Huh?
Where the hell did he come from?
Damn it all. It didn't hit him.
Can it be?
Saddlecloth 990 Sandman comes out of
nowhere to claim the lead on foot.
They're approaching the end of the slope.
Woo-hoo!
We are 17 action correct
minutes into this race.
Shit.
The final turn is in sight.
Once they pass these rocks, it's
a straight shot to the finish!
Oh, my!
Sandman takes a shortcut right through!
Look at him go, dear.
How is that even possible?
It's like he's more than human.
The power of the native people runs deep.
In this race across the continents,
it will serve him in good stead.
The other racers have made their descent
and are headed for the final turn!
3,800 racers, and Poco
Loco is in the lead!
Gary, we're never gonna win if
we keep staring at their asses.
It's time we got this show on the road.
Leave him in the dust.
Gyro's making his move!
Yes, he is taking the lead!
But how's he going to keep it?
There's a final 2,000-yard
straightaway after this bend!
There's so many people I have no idea
amazing look at this sea of places
here in an old church On the edge of the
wilderness profited by the center and
the headwinds tens of thousands of Fans
wait to see who wins this first leg
of the race whoever does win this race
will be a hero to the whole world.
You've run so well today and you've
been wise to save your strength.
But now we're at the finish, so let loose!
What, I can't believe it,
he's back in the running!
It's Dio,
the broken bridge stopped him in his
tracks and now he's leading the chase!
He's hitting less wind resistance
in the other racers' wakes.
That's how he caught up from so far back.
The winner gets 50 million, but I don't
give a damn about the prize money.
I'm here to prove myself to that man,
to prove I'm worthy of knowing
the secret of the Steel Balls.
The one who will beat Gyro
Zeppeli in his own game.
It's me!
Johnny, don't start!
From here until the finish,
technique isn't worth a dab.
Victory hinges on a single truth.
The strongest legs prevail!
You got up easy before
thanks to that dead cow!
So I hope you're ready to go for broke!
Poco Loco Challenge is
inside of the finish line!
Andy's back!
Sandman leaps into the final break!
It's that guy again.
Only 500 yards to go!
The Chasers know it's now or never!
It's Dio and 7 o 'clock,
9-3-9, Johnny Joestar.
They're closing in fast on Gyro,
who's closing in fast on Sandman.
He's running to beat the man
with Paul and Hunt Pursuit.
The Chasers are closing in on Gyro.
Three legs, two legs.
There it is, neck and neck.
We've got four horses neck and
neck as they fight for the lead.
Well, Johnny Joestar, I'm impressed.
Catching up to me is no easy task.
Tell me something, kid.
Have you ever been on a sailboat?
Turns out the more headwind
a sailboat catches,
the faster it cuts through the water.
You feel the Santa Ana up from Mexico?
It helps our horses do the same thing.
Allow me to demonstrate.
Space Fiber in a bare-knuckle
brawl for the lead.
100 yards to go.
Who will persevere?
It's Tyro Zeppelin.
Tyro's in the lead and what a sight.
Ease out in front and pulling ahead.
Those are the steel balls.
He used the spin of the
steel balls to spread his
cloak and gain lift through
Bernoulli's principle.
Just like the sails of a ship filled
with that headwind from Mexico.
Dero's in the lane.
He's untouchable.
50 yards to the goal. Now 30.
Not enough track to catch him anymore.
One last punch on Dario and...
He wins!
Dario simply takes the crown
For the First Nation of Dazzling Victory,
we have our first race
leader of the Steel Moron.
It was the summer of 1890, and I
was drawn to the shores of the West.
Drawn by something beautiful,
glinting amid the darkness.
I guess you could call
it the light of hope.
This is the story of how I began to walk.
Not literally, but in the sense
of walking the path to manhood.
It all began when I, Johnny Joestar,
first met a mysterious
stranger named Gyro Zeppeli.
Thank you.
Oh, ladies and gentlemen,
we just saw Jojo.
People left you right,
we never spot this place.
You can make no way, but
you must give it my one!
Jojo!
Thank you.